A dream that everyone has is to have a beautiful house and that
too in Jaipur.  Yes, people of Jaipur, now we
will become neighbours.  There is such a big hall in this house
that I can sit on the sofa set and
watch TV and if I feel like it, I can study a little
because there are so many aesthetic book
shelves here.  Now that we have AC uncle, there is
no tension of heat and look, the flowers look absolutely
real.  After that is this dining
table, right in front of which is such a beautiful mirror.
Now let me show you my cute little
kitchen, on one side of which is a
fridge.  Hmm.  Is there anything in the fridge?   I
drink some cold drink.  Cold
Peggy.  On the other side is this chimney and induction
and all the utensils and spices are kept in all the cabinets.
Hey, there's Bonavita too.  I
eat a little.  You know, like we used to steal food in our childhood.
Now let me tell you how many
rooms are there in it.  So this is the first room which is very
beautiful and simple and an office chair is also
kept here.  Next to this room is a washroom
linked to the hall and just in front of it is
another room.  But it has an attached balcony, attached
washroom and such a big cupboard.
By the way, what's on the balcony?  Trees, plants,
washing machines.  Now before showing the last room,
look at this.  We have found a table for ironing in the hall.
And brother, the last room is
so beautiful, right next to the kitchen, it has
such a big cupboard, attached washroom and attached
balcony also.  Actually, we are going to stay in this three BHK for
a week.  But my
dream is that I too should have such a
beautiful house.  Why only mine?  May all of you have such a
beautiful home.  Radhe
Radhe.